<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrey Mikheev&#39; programming blog</title>
    <link>http://mikheev.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrey Mikheev&#39; programming blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2017 Andrey Mikheev</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mikheev.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a developer.
If you wish to know more, please feel free to contact me via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributions</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/contributions/contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/contributions/contributions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSL</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/blog/first-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/blog/first-page/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hello, World!&amp;rdquo;
As this is the first blog post on this website.
This website is created using the Hugo static website generator. You define the layout of your pages using regular HTML (combined with Hugo&amp;rsquo;s templates), CSS and JavaScript and you write your pages&amp;rsquo; contents using Markdown. Hugo takes these source files and generates the HTML files for you. All you have to do afterwards is deploy these files on your server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/license/</guid>
      <description>All content on this website, unless otherwise noted, is copyright © 2017 Andrey Mikheev and licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
All code on this website, unless otherwise noted, is copyright © 2016, 2017 Andrey Mikheev and licensed under the MIT license:
 Copyright &amp;copy; 2017 Andrey Mikheev
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>Please browse through my GitHub repositories for an exhaustive list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>http://mikheev.me/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 14:43:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikheev.me/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal website. You can learn more about me, browse my own open-source projects or view my contributions to other open-source projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>